howtotrainyourdogeasily.com 2011-10-20

# 

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Collection of Information  
**We only collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology  
**The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

**Distribution of Information**  
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

**Commitment to Data Security**  
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

**Privacy Contact Information**  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

By e-mail: contact@dkodigital.com

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.

**Disclaimer**

This website is a collaborative website written by a group of individuals. This website does not accept any form of cash advertising, sponsorship, or paid topic insertions. However, we will and do accept and keep free products, services, travel, event tickets, and other forms of compensation from companies and organizations.

The compensation received will never influence the content, topics or posts made on this website. All advertising is in the form of advertisements generated by a third party ad network. Those advertisements will be identified as paid advertisements.

The owner(s) of this site is not compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. The views and opinions expressed on this website are purely the website owners. If we claim or appear to be experts on a certain topic or product or service area, we will only endorse products or services that we believe, based on our expertise, are worthy of such endorsement. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer or provider.

**Products Linked Disclaimer**

If a product or service linked to on this site has an affiliate program, you can safely bet that the link we’re using is an affiliate link. Sometimes we may get paid a commission if you purchase the product or service.

**Product Reviews Disclaimer**

The views and opinions expressed by our contributors of the product reviews are their own and not necessarily those of this website. These reviews should not be taken as recommendations but rather customer opinions of the products that they may or may not have used.

Sometimes we are sent a product to review which we do on an unbiased case by case basis. When we are sent something to review we are usually given the product, we use the product, and it is not returned. Never in any case are our opinions biased because we received the product for free to use. If we don’t like the product we will share that also. Once again the site is for the benefit of our readers and the site can only get better by building a trusting audience.

We make no warranty or representation, expressed or implied, as to the accuracy or sufficiency of the information contributed by outside sources, and assume no responsibility or liability regarding the use of such information. We do not warrant the performance, effectiveness or applicability of any materials listed or linked to our website. The information provided in the reviews is intended for educational purposes only. Use your own good judgment before you buy the product.

**Contest Disclaimer**

If we are running a contest odds are the sponsor has donated the prize and we are not compensated at all. The prize is usually donated by a sponsor and we give it away. Its that simple. We built our site based around helping our readers, if we can give them a gift from time to time you can bet we will do it.
